[Music]
[Música]
Aside from this thing Aside from this
aparte de esta movida aparte de esta
thing, there's another parallel thing between Lali
movida hay otra movida paralela de Lali
and Amanda Why Because Amanda
con Amanda Por qué Porque Amanda ha
posted a tweet Ugh Wait,
puesto un tweet Uf Espérate que el
Lali's Instagram It's dangerous Okay
Instagram de Lali Es peligroso Eh vale
Amanda posted the following tweet a year has
Amanda puso el siguiente tweet un año ha
passed and they're still behind it, I mean quoting
pasado y siguen detrás o sea citando lo
Ricky's thing Okay if you only knew the amount of
de Ricky vale si supierais la de
atrocities I've had to put up with
barbaridades que he tenido que aguantar
from these two beings
por parte de estos dos seres punto
ellipsis and Lali says this is it, I
suspensivo y dice Lali esto ya sí que no
'm not fed up with it Don't drag me into any
estoy hasta los [__] no me metáis en
more [ __ ] Amanda Tell me what have you had to
más movidas Amanda Dime qué has tenido
put up with from me beautiful if we haven't
que aguantar de mí bonita si no hemos
even exchanged half a word false
cruzado ni media palabra falsos
victimizers It's that Lali what did she
victimistas Es que la Lali qué le ha
say to Amanda what did Lali say to her
dicho a la a la Amanda qué le ha dicho
Lali Amanda it doesn't sound to me that she
Lali Lali Amanda no me suena que le haya
said it doesn't sound to me let's see maybe I
dicho no me suena que a ver a lo mejor
'm mistaken because I'm
me estoy equivocando porque estoy
speaking from memory eh but like like no no she
hablando de memoria eh pero como que
never said anything no
como que no no nunca le dijo nada no
come on it's that in fact it's not that it's not that she didn't
vamos es que de hecho no es que no es
say much to her she didn't
que no le dijera mucho a que no le
say anything to this girl not to
dijera nada a la a la chica esta no a la
Amanda it's that Lali  actually I don't even know
Amanda es que Lali en realidad tampoco
how I'm going to tell Ricky It's that
como que le digga a Ricky Es que de
really having to wake up on a [ __ ]
verdad tener que despertarme un [__]
Sunday and see that shitty tweet Amanda
domingo y ver ese tweet de [__] Amanda
Lopez my love show it some of the
López cariño mío enseña alguna
crap that you've had to put up with
barbaridad que hayas tenido que aguantar
from me show it so much that you talk show it let's
de mí enséñala tanto que hablas enséñala
see what crap you've had to put
a ver qué barbaridad has tenido que
up with from me a year has passed and they're still
aguantar de mí un año ha pasado y siguen
behind him he's your boyfriend he's your boyfriend who
detrás es tu novio es tu novio el que
keeps talking about me I swear girl I understand that it
sigue hablando de mí que yo te lo juro
bothers you I understand that it
tía entiendo que te moleste entiendo que
bothers you that your boyfriend mentions me
te moleste que tu novio me nombre
constantly has he changed his voice
constantemente le ha cambiado la la voz
to alali or what I don't know I see it very different
a alali o qué No sé la veo muy diferente
it's super different Yupi jupi to javy
es super diferente Yupi jupi al javy
Yupi to Javi well good Thank you thank you thank you Yes yes yes yes
Yupi al Javi bueno buen Gracias gracias
yes the face well the
gracias Sí sí sí sí sí la cara bueno la
face no Let's see it's that in the end I understand
cara no A ver es que al final entiendo
that at those ages you change a lot
que con esas edades se se cambia mucho
not from one year to another or whatever
no de unos años para otros o lo que sea
but yes the voice says naf voice from the
pero sí que la voz dice naf voz de
lower neighborhood let's see The Voice the voice It's
barrio bajera a ver La Voz la voz Es
different from ours really no but don't
diferente a la de nuestra verdad no pero
hold me responsible for what
que no me hagáis responsable de lo que
others do what
hagan los demás que lo que hagan los
others do with their lives  It's not my fault Leave it
demás con su vida no es culpa mía Dejad
Ah she's voice today yesterday she had it
Ah que está fónica hoy que ayer la tenía
fine Says luare luare luare the bastard
bien Dice luare luare luare el cabrón se
knows every blink of every [ __ ]
sabe cada pestañeo de cada [__]
influencer eh let me live that the one who has been
influencer eh de vivir dejadme vivir que
putting up with messages for a [ __ ] year of I wish she
la que lleva un [__] año aguantando
saw you I wish you die
mensajes de ojalá te vio Ojalá te mueras
kill yourself it's me so stop playing the
suicídate soy yo así que dejaos de
victim and especially you Amanda that
victimismo y sobre todo tú Amanda que
nobody gave you to see at this funeral to
nadie te dado ver en este entierro para
begin with eh it's true if the other day
empezar eh es verdad si el otro día la
we heard her the other day we reacted to something
escuchamos el otro día reaccionamos algo
about her and she was in a different way it's
de ella y estaba de otra manera es
true eh luare frame No for the
verdad eh luare fotograma No para la
mini frame for the mini I didn't
mini fotograma para la mini no lo he
catch it by accident Okay Oh they've been going on for a year
pillado sin querer Okay Ay un año llevan
and they're still after Eh no I mean it's not that what
y siguen detrás Eh no O sea no es que ya
I was missing if
lo que me faltaba si de verdad os está
this situation is really bothering you so much
molestando tanto esta situación sobre
especially you dear that
todo a ti querida que deja de hablar de
your boyfriend stops talking about me that your boyfriend stops talking about me
mí tu novio que deje de hablar de mí tu
How many videos are there on YouTube of me
novio Cuántos vídeos hay en YouTube míos
talking about him that I have talked about
hablando de él qué he hablado en
live because my [ __ ] swells and I have
directos porque se me hincha el [__] y
said four things Well yes but it's that
he dicho cuatro cosas Pues sí pero es
your boyfriend has been a year  and he did
que tu novio ha pasado un año y ha hecho
a podcast with I don't know who talking about
un podcast con no sé quién hablando de
me a debate with Dallas talking about me
mí un debate con Dallas hablando de mí
too in fact in the podcast he did
también de hecho en el podcast que hizo
with delox Ricky was talking about Ricky, he was talking
con delox Ricky hablaba de Ricky hablaba
about Lali sucking his dick I don't know
de de que Lali le chupado la [__] no sé
what I don't know how much, I mean Ricky I think he
qué no sé cuánto o sea Ricky yo creo que
's not aware of the things he's
no es consciente de las cosas que le ha
done to Lali uh he's gone a little
hecho a Lali eh se le ha ido un poco la
overboard he's gone a little overboard
mano se le ha ido un poco la la manilla
Hey but are we going to reach 3000
Oye pero vamos a llegar a los 3000
members this year or end up stopping the
miembros este año o acabar paremos el
year and we won't reach 3000 members
año y no llegaremos a los 3000 miembros
it's too much of a setup by Ricky well Please
est too un montaje de Ricky bien Por
please don't jump on the
favor por favor no te subas tú al carro
victim bandwagon now of I've put up with
ahora de victimista de he aguantado
atrocities of this invite Alin I
barbaridades de esto invita al Alin Yo
have invited her many times eh I mean
la he invitado muchas veces eh o sea
many times at times I have invited her I invited her
muchas veces a alguna vez la he invitado
at the time I
la invité en su momento la invité
also invited her when the subject came up again
también cuando volvió a surgir el tema y
and she doesn't want she doesn't want to talk she's
y ella no quiere no quiere hablar ella
going to take measures I think uh both don't
va a tomar medidas creo eh los dos no me
involve me don't involve me and don't make things up Bring out the
metas no me metas y no inventes Saca las
atrocities bring them out let's see because I
barbaridades sácalas a ver porque es que
know what  you're going to take out and it's a story
sé lo que vas a sacar y es una historia
of best friends it's the only thing you can
de mejores amigos es lo único que puedes
get out of me take it out and I'll answer that
sacar de mí sacarla y yo respondo a eso
too and if you wanted someone knows
también y ya si quisis alguien sabe a
what she means with those stories for
qué se refiere con esas historias para
best friends What does she mean with
mejores amigos A qué se referirá con
those stories for best friends
esas historias para mejores amigos
take them out and I'll answer that too there I
sacarlas y os respondo a eso también ahí
stayed arlar this like mature
me quedé arlar esto como personas
and normal adults that I know you are not
adultas maduras y normales que sé que no
but if I wanted what's
lo sois pero si quisiera qué culpa tiene
Amanda's fault that a broccoli hair friend of yours
Amanda para que un pelo brócoli amego ti
an insurance goes around threatening them on the
un seguro vaya amenazándolos por la
street these are out of step with life
calle estos están desfasados de la vida
Well but that was done by the
Bueno pero eso lo ha hecho el pelo
broccoli hair he didn't do it he didn't do it
brócoli no lo ha hecho no lo ha hecho
Lali come on eh I want to think that Lali
Lali vamos eh yo quiero pensar que Lali
when she found out that her friend
cuando se ha enterado que el amigo ha
did that she said to him you you you what the
hecho eso le ha dicho tú tú t tú qué
[ __ ] are you doing in fact I remember
[__] haces de hecho me acuerdo que
when that boy said in a live stream that he
cuando ese chico dijo en un directo que
wanted to hit me too that
que me quería pegar a mí también que no
I don't remember why he wanted to hit me I don't know
me acuerdo por qué me quería pegar no sé
why he wanted to hit me but he said
por qué me quería pegar pero decía
When I see him I'm going to hit him it's not worth it and he
Cuando lo vea le voy a pegar no vale y
said you you you calm down you know how to do it
le dijo t tu tu tú calma sabes hacerlo
we live 5 minutes apart Hello  Ricky you
vivimos a 5 minutos Hola Ricky me
told me on a call that I was never going to be
dijiste en una llamada que nunca me iba
able to afford to live in Andorra here
a poder permitir vivir en andorra aquí
I am we're neighbors uncle Ricky
estoy somos vecinos tío el Ricky
talking about pat to his girlfriend when he's
hablándole de pat a la novia cuando se
fighting you never know the things and the
pelea vete tú a saber la las cosas y las
calls and stuff that Ali has saved
llamadas y demás que tiene Ali guardada
from Ricky from Ricky making fun of me
de Ricky de Ricky vacilándome
[Music]
[Música]
allow to live in Andorra what do you know
permitir vivir andorra qué sabes tú
who you are [ __ ] Well yeah let's see Lali what
quién eres [__] Pues sí a ver Lali qué
is it that you do ol fan everyone wants to
es lo que hace ol fan todos te quieren
hit you Javi it's also true that's why
pegar Javi también es verdad por eso
I'm training cilito it's also
estoy entrenando cilito también es
true But what does he do with only no
verdad Pero a qué se dedica al only no
pure and hard only can't we meet for
puro y duro only no podemos quedar a
a coffee and talk things out and
echar un café y hablamos las cosas y se
the problem will end that I know it's not going to
acaba el problema que yo sé que no va a
happen I know it's not going to happen Hey
pasar Yo sé que no va a pasar Eh
little parenthesis I'm not doing it to
paréntesis pequeño no lo hago para
hit them or to do anything bad to them that
pegarles ni para hacerles nada malo que
these two are my special and they're
que son mi especialito estos dos y ya
going to say that I want to beat them up
van a decir que les quiero partir la
nothing to do with it I'm
cara nada que ver lo estoy diciendo en
serious Because I've been [ __ ] fed up a [ __ ]
serio Porque estoy hasta el [__] un [__]
year monetizing a [ __ ] lie that
año monetizando una [__] mentira que
even if what he says were true it's been
aunque fuera verdad lo que dice ha
a year Ricky a year has passed and you're
pasado un año Ricky ha pasado un año y
still talking about me you have  your girlfriend
sigues hablando de mí tienes a tu novia
next to you normal guy who has to
al lado tío normal que tenga que hacer
tweet playing the [ __ ] victim must be
twit haciéndose la [__] víctima tiene
fed up with hearing about
que estar hasta el [__] de escuchar
me [ __ ] I don't want to mention
hablar de mí [__] no quiero mencionar
anyone but there are certain couples who
a nadie pero hay cierta parej que
also suffer from this but let's see if it's
también sufren esto pero a ver sí que es
true eh I mean how the hell are you going to spend
verdad eso eh o sea cómo [__] vas a
so much time talking about your ex with
estar tanto tiempo hablando de tu ex con
your new partner and that a large part of your
tu nueva pareja y que gran parte de tu
content is based on your ex and your new
contenido se base en tu ex y tu nueva
partner there you know I mean I don't know yeah yeah yeah it's
pareja ahí sabes o sea no sé sí sí sí sí
like but yeah two days ago she was
que es como pero siali hace dos días
also throwing barbs nafay I understand
también la tiraba puas nafay entiendo
that on this side in this one
que en este bando en esta tampoco
we are not on the same side but mm No
estamos en el mismo bando pero mm No
she two days ago in that
ella hace dos días en aquel directo
last live she did she was responding to
último que hizo estaba respondiendo a
Ricky's lies about her I mean
mentiras de Ricky sobre ella o sea es
Ricky started saying Ricky started
que Ricky se puso a decir Ricky se puso
saying that he that Lali had asked him for
a decir que él que Lali le había pedido
forgiveness that he had spoken to
perdón a él que él había hablado con
Lali that Lali had asked
Lali que Lali le había pedido perdón a
him for forgiveness and that things were good and that she didn't
él y que la cosa estaba bien y que no
have fimosi and it's like dude she's making everything up damn It's that it's that I
tenía fimosi y es como tío tod está
understand her My poor thing but leave me
entiendo Pobrecita mía pero dejadme en
alone and don't  you put more in your
paz y no me metáis más en vuestras
[ __ ] And well the
[__] Y bueno ya está aquí el
statement is here I'm so sorry I never
comunicado lo siento muchísimo nunca
talk like this for stories but it's that Real
hablo así por historias pero es que Real
just opened an eye and I've already seen
que acaba de abrir un ojo y ya he visto
the [ __ ] shitty tweet that you play the
el [__] tweet de [__] que te hagas la
victim Amanda really honey what is that
victima tú Amanda de verdad cariño que
I am admitted to the [ __ ]
es que yo esty ingresada en el [__]
hospital for this issue do you understand that
hospital por este tema me entiendes que
if we start playing the
es que si nos ponemos a hacernos las
victims I'm going to be in for a while my life is going to be in
víctimas tengo para rato mi vida tengo
for a while So I repeat leave me alone
para rato Así que repito dejadme en paz
Amanda take out those atrocities that you've
Amanda saca esas barbaridades que has
had to put up with from me don't
tenido que aguantar de mí de mí no me
make me responsible for what
hagáis responsable de lo que hagan
third parties do but Take out the
terceras personas pero Saca las
atrocities that you've had to put up with
barbaridades que has tenido que aguantar
from me because you can only take out the
de mí porque solo puedes sacar la
story of best friends that we
historia de mejores amigos que
need that story of best
necesitamos esa historia de mejores
friends eh we need that story of
amigos eh necesitamos esa historia de
best friends man well I do think
mejores amigos hombre pues Yo sí pienso
perfectly well that that that Ricky
perfectamente que que que que Ricky
lied about the Lali issue a lot
mintiera sobre el tema Lali un montón
but yes there are a ton of lies
pero si es que hay un montón de mentiras
look the first thing is that Ricky deals
mira lo primero es que Ricky se maneja
with lies we've already seen that with
en mentira eso ya lo hemos visto con
everything with everything so by heart eh by
todo con todo así de memoria eh de
heart restraining order
memoria orden de alejamiento principal
Ricky's main lie that the restraining order  the
mentira de Ricky que la orden de
separation was in
alejamiento estaba en instancias
higher courts that Lali invented a
superiores que Lali se inventó una
rape he invented it regarding the
violación se la inventó él respecto al
issue of when he searched her phone he
tema de cuando le registró el teléfono
has given four versions First it was that he
ha dado cuatro versiones Primero era que
took her phone and read her a bunch
le cogió el teléfono y le leó un montón
of conversations where he caught her cheating
de conversaciones donde pilló los
Where there were deleted messages I don't
cuernos Donde había mensajes borrados no
know what I don't know how much then that he
sé qué no sé cuánto luego que que que le
took her phone and read a
cogió el teléfono y le yó una
conversation then that what he saw was an
conversación luego que lo que vio fue un
audio he has given three or four
audio ha dado tres o cuatro versiones
different versions that I closed the live
diferentes que yo cerré el directo
abruptly He even edited the extract the
bruscamente Incluso editó el extracto el
clip to make it look like So I closed
clip para que pareciera Así que yo cerré
the live abruptly in which I was
el directo bruscamente en el que estaba
with Pablo okay because dala was
con Pablo vale porque dala nos estaba
sending us WhatsApp so that you close
mandando Whatsapp para que cerrás demos
the live because we were talking about
el directo porque estábamos hablando de
his contracts what more lies guys it was it's
sus contratos qué más mentiras chicos
always lie after lie it
era es que siempre mentira tras mentira
's all the time all the time lie
es todo el tiempo todo el tiempo mentira
after lie yes the thing about 3 in the afternoon the thing about the
tras mentira sí lo de las 3 de la tarde
police station closing at 3
lo de la que la comisaría cierra a las 3
in the afternoon and it can't be done and no they
de la tarde y no se puede y no no le
can't arrest Dallas after
pueden detener a Dallas a partir de las
3 in the afternoon everything everything eh with the
3 de la tarde todo todo eh con lo de los
hitman of I mean Ricky  they handle
sicario de o sea Ricky se manejan
lies then you go and know the
mentira entonces vete tú a saber la de
things that Lali will have that Ricky
cosas que Lali tendrá que Ricky haya
lied about her I know I am in the subject Lali
mentido sobre ella yo s yo en tema Lali
against Ricky I am with Lali and it is not
contra Ricky estoy con Lali y no es
because I have a problem with Ricky
porque yo tenga m problema con con Ricky
Well look however now what
Pues mira sin embargo ahora lo lo que le
Ali's friend has done to Ricky well it
ha hecho el amigo de Ali a Ricky pues me
seems terrible to me you understand me I repeat best
parece fatal me entiendes repito mejores
friends take it out and I will respond too I
amigos sácala y yo respondo también
need to know what it is eh To
necesito eso saber qué es lo que es eh A
what you are going to say about that story but I
lo que vais a decir de esa historia pero
assure you that neither
os aseguro que no os gustar la respuesta
you nor your boyfriend will like the answer what will it
ni a ti y ni mucho menos a tu novio qué
be I need that Eh I need that eh See you
será necesito eso Eh Necesito eso eh
later A kiss And on top of that it saves me
Hasta luego Un beso Y encima me ahorra
the story Hahaha What was I putting to see
la historia a mí Jajaja Qué ponía a ver
really I can't stand that
de verdad que no aguanto más que tenga
this clown has to come and say that she has
que venir esta payasa a decir que ha
had to put up with things from me after
tenido que aguantar cosas de mi después
what I have put up with for a year it is
de lo que llevo aguantado yo un año
balls that she shows something about
manda [__] que muestre alguna cosa de
me to her If your boyfriend has her he has been
mí hacia ella Si la tiene tu novio lleva
naming her constantly for a year dear I understand
un año nombrá constantemente querida
that you [ __ ] but don't make up
entiendo que te jodas pero no inventes
[ __ ] leave me alone [ __ ]  crazy
[__] dejadme en paz [__] locos
obsessives and don't make me responsible for
obsesos y no me hagáis responsable de
things that others do live your
cosas que hagan los demás vivid vuestra
life you see it doesn't agree with what
vida lo veis no está de acuerdo con lo
the friend has done and your relationship
que ha hecho el amigo y vuestra relación
calm down and forget about me already
tranquilos y olvidaros ya de mí que ha
a [ __ ] year has passed get over yourself already [ __ ]
pasado un [__] año supérame ya [__]
coo And why did they erase that eh Lali
coo Y por qué le han borrado eso eh Lali
Lali Lali Lali we know each other stay
Lali Lali Lali que nos conocemos estate
still
quieta
[Music]
[Música]